All right, and welcome to the course.
And before we continue, let's address the elephant in the room the course requirements, since this
is an advanced course.
My expectation is that you are already familiar with React and A.j.'s fundamentals since, in my opinion,
when it comes to learn, it's really about combining our existing frontend and server knowledge instead
of starting everything from the blank page.
So in other words, this is not a course where we'll cover React or Node.js just from scratch.
Simply because it would take way too long.
And it would be very unfair to the people who are already familiar with both technologies.
As far as the react, like I already mentioned, I'm assuming that you already know the fundamentals.
For example, water is a component.
And on top of that, you are familiar with react hooks.
Know how to implement the most used ones.
So think you state?
Use the fact use reducer and use context, and also, you know, how to create global context in your
React application.
When it comes to server, I'm assuming that you can set up a basic server, create controllers and or
else have a MongoDB Atlas account.
Know how to connect to it.
And lastly, have some experience with JSON web tokens.
Now, if you do need a refresher on any of these topics, I do have tons and tons of free videos where
I cover all of those things from scratch and showcase all of the steps and gotchas in great detail.
So please do not skip the following lecture and if necessary, please utilize any or all of the free
resources I provided.