We're watching the course you might experience these two following issues of the video quality goes
bananas.
And the transcript does not match exactly to what I'm saying in the video.
Please be aware that both of these issues have nothing to do with specific course or how it was recorded.
Meaning you might experience the same issues in different courses as well, and in general, instructors
have no control over such things.
So the first issue you might encounter could be a bad video quality where as you're watching, the video
screen turns blurry and it's very hard to read anything off the screen, and I'll spare you the long
explanation.
Essentially, the issue is caused by auto resolution.
Lucky for us, though, the fix is very simple.
Just click on the Settings Cog and choose 720.
Now, if your internet connection is slow, you might need to go for even lower resolution.
But for the most part, 720p will do the job.
So imagine you're watching the course, and all of a sudden video quality gets bad.
Just locate the settings cog and manually select 720p, even if you have a different value set as auto.
And the second issue you might experience is video transcript.
Being off meaning if you prefer using subtitles or you just want to read the transcript, text might
not match exactly to what I'm saying in the video again.
Instructors have no control over that, and unfortunately, at this point in time, I cannot provide
you with any possible fix for this particular issue.