And in order to follow along with the project, you will need some assets like images and CIUSSS, and
you can get them by visiting the site.
John Smeal dot com ran the URL is Dum Dum Dum Jones.
MiLB.com: And then once you hit this lovely site, keep scrolling and you're looking for the job of
my project.
Now you might find it in the latest project in the home page.
But if you don't, you'll always find it if you navigate to Project Page and then you can even filter
it more.
And look just for the man project online once you get the project, the job, if I won this link will
lead to a lot of application and I'll leave this one open since as will be building some stuff.
I'll show you the final result.
Just so you have a better understanding.
And when it comes to staff files and source code, both of them effectively lead back to the same repo,
the main course job before.
And from this point, you either want to use the clone option where effectively you're out of the URL,
or you can just download the zip.
So in my case, I'm going to go with a get clone option, so I'll just copy and then navigate back to
my computer.
We're going to go to your city, messed up.
So first I'm going to navigate the desktop and then I want to go with GIF clone and then pass in the
URL.
And once you do that, once you're able to project on your computer, you can continue with the videos.
And of course, if you're using the download option, I don't need to tell you that the zip file is
going to be here in the downloads.