And once the complete project is on your computer.
You can just take a look at it in your text editor.
Now we're not going to spin it up or anything like that, but this is going to be easier if I show you
that using Visual Studio code.
And essentially, if you want to run the application, you just need to go to read me and then follow
the steps.
So you install dependencies with this command line, you want to rename that and we temp to data entry.
And the reason why this is set up this way, so I can give you the examples of the environment variables
we are looking for, because keep in mind that we do have get a law which will ignore data enemy once
we push this up to a GitHub.
But what you want to do is rename it to adopt the entry and then you just want to provide your values
for the Mongo you URL.
Basically, this is going to be the connection string to Mongo.
There be revenge than double your secret, as well as JWT Lifetime.
Now to tell you, honestly, you only need to provide this one because if you take a look at the data
and you can say that I already provided some dummy values for JWT Secret as well as JWT Lifetime.
So the only thing you need to do is just provide connection.
String back to your MongoDB database and then you simply want to go with npm start and just answer because
I know I'll get this.
Yes, everything works.
I checked it multiple times.
Again, you just installed dependencies.
You just change it to data entry, provide the values and then run npm.
Start here in the root folder and you'll be good to go.
And then the project is going to be on localhost 3000.
Now, the reason why we actually got the application is not because I want you to spin it up on your
local machine.
It's actually because if you take a look at the client more specifically source, you'll find this assets
one.
And in here you'll find all this, yes and images.
We're going to use during the project because what you need to understand is that when it comes to these
bigger projects, I mean, if will build everything from scratch, meaning success as well as get all
the images is you're going to take way longer.
So yes, of course, will type out all the logic when it comes to front end as well as the back and
the server.
But when it comes to a look of the application, basically yes, yes, yes, I provided already all
the resources.
Now you don't need to do anything right now financially in a videos.
I'll show you where and how I want you to set up this assets folder.
And lastly, one more reason why I wanted you to get the complete project.
Because that way, if you ever run into some bugs, you can just simply come here, take a look at my
code and troubleshoot it faster.