Beautiful.
And once we're familiar with the final application, let's start working on our own project.
And the first task might look somewhat trivial where we all need to set up an empty folder.
So basically come up with the name of your application and name the folder our way, and they will set
up a read me the first.
In my case, I'm going to do that unless of course, you can set it up anywhere you like, and I'm just
going to go with the same name.
I'm going to go with a job.
For one, I'm going to open up my visual studio code, my text editor, and like I said, first file
that I want to set up here is actually read me.
So I'm going to go with read me and not let me go all uppercase.
Read me and markdown.
And the idea behind this file is falling.
Before each video, I will share all the steps I'm going to take.
So that way, if you want to complete the task on your own, it's definitely an option.
I use that approach in one of the projects in my adult course.
And students seem to really like it.
One quick side note, though, if there's a discrepancy between what you see in the video and the content
in your read me, please follow your lead me content since I probably fixed it after I recorded the
video in order to get all the steps.
Navigate to Final Project.
Look for me in the source and what you can do is take this whole thing.
Copy and paste it over here.
And once you have the project, we have a read in place.
Now we can proceed to the next step.