OK.
And the first thing that I want to do is to set up a React application.
And the way we'll do that will create a clean folder in the road here.
So right next to the read me will open up the terminal.
Now, technically, you can do it using your computer terminal, but in my case, I'm going to use the
integrated one, the one that is available in a visual studio code.
We want to navigate to the folder.
We're just grid.
So see the client and that will create a boilerplate React application by running and perks.
And the command is Create React app.
And then we go with Dart, which essentially just means that the name is going to be exactly the same
as the folder where we were working.
And so in our case now it is going to be a client now that will take a little bit of time.
So most likely, I will pass the video while the install takes place.
And then once I'm done, I'm going to set up error and browser side by side.
That is usually my preference as I'm working, so I where I can show you the immediate things on a small
screen and then if I ever need to showcase something on a big screen, I can just navigate here as well.
And then lastly, I'll show you where I want you to copy and paste, and I'll talk about why it's so
important.
The assets from the complete project.
So let's get cracking on the first thing.
Like I said, I want to create a folder.
I'm going to call this client on line open terminal the integrated one.
The shortcut is control and tilde.
And then we want to go here with City Client.
So now we're navigating through that folder.
And once we're here, I said the commanders NPCs create React app, and no, which essentially is going
to set up that boilerplate React application.
And like I mentioned previously, this is going to take a little bit of time.
So I will stop the video on all resume once everything is up and running.
And as a quick side note, if you get this error while running, NPCs create React app.
One of the possible solutions is to add later to the command so the entire command you're looking for
is going to be and B, X or Y create React app and you want to add app and latest and whatever the name
of the project.
So in my case, I'm just going to go with project name.
So if you get this error, try running this command instead.
And once you do that, everything should work as expected.
And once we have our React application, plesch think I forgot to add one more step where essentially
we want to open up the dev server.
And if we take a look at the package JSON, the command is npm start.
So let me add that intrigued me where I'll go with npm start.
And then since I'm already in a client, what I can simply do is just type and PM start.
So now we're spinning up the def server.
And like I said, I'm going to set them up side by side.
Now you don't have to, but I already explained my reasoning for that.
So let me make this one smaller for now.
The same is going to be with this one.
And I'm just going to set them side by side now, this is a Mac thing.
So this has nothing to do with Visual Studio code or anything like that.
So we'll set them side by side.
Now there's a bunch of boilerplate code which will effectively remove in the following videos.
And the last thing that I actually want to do here is get those assets.
Now it's very important that you copy and paste because what you need to keep in mind that the project,
the complete project, is still using those resources.
So if you'll just go here, take the assets, basically remove them and place it in your current project.
Yeah.
Everything is going to work in the current project, but if you ever try to spin up the complete one?
Well, there's going to be some bugs.
So what I want you to do is navigate to the complete project.
Again, we're looking for a client.
Then more specifically, we're looking for source.
And then the assets.
So in my case, I'm going to copy this folder and then we want to navigate back to our current project.
So my guess job for that client and then the source.
And then just based the folder.
So now I have my assets in my project.
Again, very, very important that you leave the assets still in the complete one if you ever want to
spin up the final project.
So in my case, I'm just going to double check now in the source I should have assets.
And if you have everything in place, same as me, then we can move on to the next step, which is going
to be cleaning out of the boilerplate code in our React application.