And once her boilerplate application is running on local three thousand next, I want to do some spring
cleaning more in the sauce.
I want you to remove abscesses.
App that's dress logo, 3G port, where vitals as well as set up test and then we need to fix, address
as well as index Jess because there are some imports and we're relying on those files.
So let's just start by removing some stuff.
I'm going to go with the lead.
So we're going to remove this one abscess.
And, you know, I think I can just combine them.
So and I also want to go with these two.
Let's just remove all of them here.
And then, like I said, we want to fix the imports were in the U.S., we're not going to be looking
for the US one on logo.
And as far as the return, I just said a simple ending, one with job or whatever is the name of your
application.
And let's also navigate through the next jazz.
And here what's remove the web vitals and also can remove all of this code.
So once we save, eventually we should see here a job of fire.
And we have everything in place now we can move on to a next step.