Beautiful.
And while we're still warming up, let's do another two easy ones first, let's change the title.
It's not.
It's going to be the title of your application again.
My Microsoft is going to be job offering.
And second, we also want to replace that little icon right next to the title.
And first, let's start with the title.
And basically, the way we do that, we just navigate to a public folder.
So this sucker over here.
And more specifically in the in the search there, now we're looking for the title tags online as far
as the favorite on the new one.
The one that I'm going to be using is located in the assets, man, more specifically in the images.
And you're looking for favicon.
I go online.
I'll show you the resource where you can get one for yourself.
So I guess let's start with a title first.
Like I said, we're going to navigate to an exceptional for time being.
I'll close the sidebar and then we're basically looking for title tags in the hat element.
And then instead of React app, I'm just going to type my favorite job offer.
So I should do it when you want to.
Like I said, take the favorite favicon from the images.
And in this case, of course, you can copy and paste if you want, but in my case, I'm just going
to drag and drop.
So you want to get the favor.
I call from the images into a public one.
That's the goal.
So let's move there to ask whether we want to replace it, if we do online, the moment we do that.
Now, as we get the favicon as well as the title, actually, we can close the index and the amount.
We're not going to need it, at least not for now.
And then as far as the resource, if you ever want to get one for yourself, I enjoy using this one,
the favor con eoe.
So once you navigate their.
You don't have these options.
And I guess I'm usually going with a text one online, and here you can provide the text color and you
can read the rest.
And once you're ready, you can just download online.
You'll get the zip file basically online, you can crack it open and then notice somewhere there is
going to be a favicon icon.
You can add it to your project and you're good to go.
So that should do it for the title on Facebook.com.
So if you have the same result, now we're going to move on to the next step.